e-xact.com 2005-03-06

# E-xact Transactions Ltd. - Privacy Statement

E-xact Transactions Ltd. has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to consumer rights to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: [www.e-xact.com](http://www.e-xact.com/)

  **Information We Collect & How it’s Used**   
Because we are a certified transaction processor we strongly uphold the privacy and security of our clients’ information which includes banking, credit card, and merchant account information. Such information is kept exclusively between our clients, E-xact Transactions, and our processing resources.

  **Information You Explicitly Provide** **via Information Request**   
We make available company literature for customers who request it, should they prefer not to download this information and/or want our print literature. We require your consent via our Information Request form or email.

**via Members’ Login**   
Access to the Member’s Area of E-xact's website requires active membership with E-xact Transactions. Valid username and password are required to enter and this area is SSL secured. A demo account (for testing purposes only) is available for individuals who register for it. Contact information to register for the demo include name, email address, phone number, address, fax number, and domain names. Registration information is used to send email "thank yous" and enable the demo for the user. This information is not shared with anyone outside of E-xact unless verbal or written permission is given by the E-xact member.

**Information We Automatically Collect** **IP Addresses**   
E-xact’s website logs IP addresses and browser types for systems administration purposes and these logs will be analyzed to improve the value of the materials available on the website. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable. This means that a user’s session will be tracked, but the user will be anonymous.

  **Cookies**   
E-xact’s website is cookie free, with the exception of our Members' Only area where cookies are used for security purposes. 

**Sharing of Information  
**This site does not supplement the information that you provide with information that is received from third parties. The only time information is shared is during your registration with E-xact for our services as this process requires third party involvement (i.e. your bank, your developer, and your possible E-xact partner affiliates). E-xact does not take responsibility or liability for how third parties secure your information once it has been passed on.

**Security**   
Protecting your privacy and information is a top priority at E-xact. We have taken careful measures to secure your information and our physical premises. This website has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Our registration and Members’ areas have SSL protection and Verisign has supplied us with a digital certificate for our website. All personal and company data referring to account applications and registration is kept in strictest confidence and security.

  **External Links  
**The E-xact website contains links to other websites and [www.e-xact.com](http://www.e-xact.com/) is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.

**E-mail Links**   
We use email links located throughout our website to allow you to contact us directly with any questions or comments you may have. We read every message sent in and try to reply promptly to each one. This information is used to respond directly to your questions or comments. We may also file your comments to improve the site or review and discard them. Your personal information is only shared with third parties, if necessary to address your question or with your explicit permission.

**Choice/Opt-Out Policy  
**This site gives users the following options for removing information from our database to not receive future communications.

You can send email to comments@e-xact.com

  You can send mail to the following postal address:       
304-134 Abbott Street  
Vancouver, BC  
V6B 2K4 Canada

  **E-xact Information Updates  
**If you no longer wish to receive updates on E-xact’s promotions and services, please send your request to be removed from our mailing list to: [comments@e-xact.com](mailto:comments@e-xact.com)

**Correct/Update Policy  
**This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided.

You can send email to comments@e-xact.com

  You can send mail to the following postal address:        
304-134 Abbott Street  
Vancouver, BC  
V6B 2K4 Canada

Call the following telephone number: (604) 691-1670

**E-xact Updates**   
If you would like to correct and/or update the contact information that you submitted to receive updates on E-xact, please send your corrections/updates to : [comments@e-xact.com](mailto:comments@e-xact.com)

**Members’ Only Site  
**If you would like to correct and/or update the contact information you entered into our Member’s area, or If you have forgotten your password and/or username please contact E-xact by e-mail ([support@e-xact.com](mailto:support@e-xact.com)) or phone (604) 691-1670

**Changes in E-xact's Privacy Policy  
**E-xact Transactions Ltd. will obtain written or active email consent from the user if the use of the information collected from the user is in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection.

**Contacting the Website  
**If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, you can contact our Webmaster at: webmaster@e-xact.com or mail us at:

E-xact Transactions Ltd.  
304-134 Abbott Street  
Vancouver, BC  
V6B 2K4 Canada
